to change myself physically Look, I have to
de cambiarme físicamente Mira total
say one thing here, a
tengo que decir aquí una cosa un
personal trainer in Seville who comes
entrenador personal en Sevilla que venga
here to my house, to my gym, eh, talking
aquí a mi casa a mi gimnasio eh hablando
about Seville. Maybe I'll be there the
en Sevilla A lo mejor estoy ahí el
first weekend of June Javier, maybe we can
primer fin de junio Javier igual nos
meet up in person, why because I've been
desvirtualizamos por qué porque me han
given invitations to the
dado invitaciones para el concierto de
Manuel Carrasco concert and maybe I'll go with a
Manuel Carrasco y a lo mejor voy con un
couple of friends there. What do you think in
par de amigas allí Qué te parece en
June? So if you're there, we'll meet up in person.
junio Entonces si estás nos
Of course, but you'll have to
desvirtualizaremos Claro pero tendrás
go to where I am because you
que acercarte tú a donde esté yo que
're my guest. In June, it's
para eso eres mi invitado en junio es
good, we didn't have a government in
bueno no teníamos nosotros gobierno en
Madrid in June. Yes, but that's the
Madrid en junio Sí pero ese es el
second. Oh, well, look, maybe we can
segundo Ah pues mira igual nos podemos
see each other two weekends in a row. Imagine it's
ver dos fin de seguidos Imagínate que es
romantic, it's
romántico
nice, it's nice, it's not nice, it's
es bonito es bonito no es bonito es
nice, well, let's see. Hey, we've spoken with
bonito bueno a ver Oye hemos hablado con
Rocío Flores, we haven't spoken, it was
Rocío Flores no hemos hablado ha sido
brief, but we're
breve pero
not going to tell you yet because no,
no lo vamos a contar todavía porque no
because now is when I, as owner of the
porque ahora es cuando yo como dueña del
Channel, say a thousand likes and almost 4,000
Canal digo mil likes y casi 4.000
people, thousands and four, this is already in its
personas miles y cuatro esto ya es de
time. Let's
época
see, I'm going to see the members, simply
a ver voy a ver los miembros simplemente
four thousand members, at least not
cuatro mil miembros por lo menos no
Marina,
marina
4,000 members, should, should, we
4.000 miembros debería deberían
should have.  4,000 members here at
deberíamos tener 4.000 miembros aquí por
least not here of members it's the
lo menos no aquí de miembros está la
thing I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you
cosa te lo digo te lo digo te lo digo
1081 eye eye and that's very good Javi they
1081 ojo ojo y eso está muy bien Javi
are saying we have to consider
están diciendo tenemos que plantearnos
the tour I'm telling you very seriously
lo de la gira te lo digo muy en serio
as you are leaving it there you do not stop
como lo estás dejando ahí no paras de
creating ideas lollipops and things and the tour
crear ideas piruletas y cosas y la gira
and inviting Marta I risk but I do not
y de invitar a Marta arriesgo pero yo no
know
sé
a tour
una gira
man let's see not a tour like Luis
hombre a ver no una gira como Luis
Miguel But well then
Miguel Pero bueno pues
leave the house
salir de casa
Look Javi you did not want to lose your belly
Mira Javi tú no querías bajar la panza
so move from the City You'll see how you
pues muévete de Ciudad Ya verás cómo lo
lose it but our target audience I
bajas pero nuestro público objetivo yo
think they are in Seville no Of course
creo que están en Sevilla no Claro claro
I think this is the Macarena in
yo creo que esta es la Macarena en
particular not the one just kidding I'm joking let's see I
concreto no la de broma es broma a ver
have no [ __ ] idea how
no tengo ni [__] idea de cómo se hace
that is done I don't know if I think seeing is the one who
eso no sé si creo que al ver es el que
has managed to do something like that Ah but
ha llegado a hacer algo de eso Ah pero
they have managed to do let's see he did it in
han llegado a hacer a ver lo hizo en
Barcelona I do not know how it will be done let's see I do
Barcelona no sé cómo se hará eso a ver
not know what kind of
no sé qué tipo de
arrangements have to be made to do
gestiones hay que hacer para para hacer
something like that if someone knows that I see
algo así si alguien sabe que me Yo veo
the messages a personal trainer I
los mensajes un entrenador personal
need and it appears by email by  the
necesito y aparece por email por lo
same someone who organizes this type of
mismo alguien que organice este tipo de
things well tell us and we do it no I
cosas pues que nos digas y lo hacemos no
mean do you think we would fill it let's
O sea tú crees que llenaríamos
see it depends on maybe a lounge
a ver depende el que a lo mejor un salón
a lounge in a bar Yes but I don't know it depends
un salón de un bar Sí pero no sé depende
there Come on then let's go Valencia let's go
ahí Venga pues vamos Valencia vamos para
there we're there this Saturday it would
allá estamos allí este sábado
only be a shame it wouldn't give much technique it would
solo daría pena no daría mucha técnica
give much technique but no I don't think so
daría mucha técnica pero no yo creo que
Eh I think not
no Eh Yo creo que no
to the beach to the one in Benidorm also to
a la playa al del benidorm también
ride or ride or ride a bus that we
montar o montar o montar un autobús que
take
llevamos
everything is to talk about it everything is to talk about it by
todo es hablarlo todo es hablarlo por
the way I have to say before entering the
cierto he de decir antes de entrar en
plank that you remember when here I asked
plancha que os acordáis cuando aquí pedí
half jokingly that it was half joking
medio coña real que era medio coña
a punching bag
un saco de boxeo
It's that I'm telling you that
Es que es que te lo estoy diciendo que
no no no no but stop a guy from this
no no no no pero stop un chico de este
chat who is called j and I
chat que se llama j y no me acuerdo del
don't remember his last name he has like a sports shop he sent the bag to my house and I have the bag on the terrace In the absence of drilling and putting the support and everything no no no I don't want to say it and you don't
no no no no lo quiero decir y no te
remember the kid's name J the
acuerdas del nombre del chaval J el
last name is not what I don't remember
apellido no es lo que no me acuerdo
a punching bag that has already
un saco de boxeo que ya se me ha
given away
regalado
and like super excited I am like I
y como súper emocionada que estoy como
still can't believe I have it here his
todavía no me lo creo que lo tenga aquí
name is j and his Instagram I'm going to tell you
se llama j y su Instagram voy a decir
what it is
cómo es
for what are you telling me
para que tú me estás diciendo
if you're telling me that they're giving you
si tú me estás diciendo que te regalan
a punching bag and you don't remember the
un saco de boxeo y no te acuerdas del
kid's name I'm telling you his name is
nombre del chaval te estoy diciendo que
jota
se llama jota
You want me to send you a
Tú quieres que yo te mando una bolsa de
Teresa salseo bag for the beach
Teresa salseo para la playa
and when I send it to you you won't remember
y cuando te la mande no te acuerdas
Look, it's called
Mira se llama
the idea Wait Wait Wait Wait it's called Wait Wait Wait
la idea Espérate Espérate Espérate se
being spontaneous is what it has to do with his name
el ser espontáneo es lo que tiene a ver
please jota Pires and he's a
se llama por favor jota Pires y es fan
Telcel fan I mean a huge fan Well in
de Telcel o sea fan máximo Bueno de
fact he called himself barbajota okay
hecho él se hacía Llamar barbajota vale
that must be
que debe
annoying okay okay okay And
[__]
really And really it is
vale vale vale Y de verdad Y de verdad
that he has a store called
es que tiene una tienda que se llama
Sporting punto es And from there he
Sporting punto es Y desde ahí me ha
sent me his bag
mandado su saco
here
aquí
Jonathan okay yes I am a disaster
Jonathan vale que si soy un desastre
Look how spontaneous things come out and I
Fíjate que me salen las espontaneidad y
forget I don't know I don't see
se me olvidan No sé no me ver para bien
things well But well it's a fantasy I
las cosas Pero bueno que una fantasía O
mean the truth is that he's a lovely boy
sea que la verdad que chico encantador
super good  McDonald's I'm like
súper bien el McDonald's estoy como
bald from having that bag but of course Now we
calva de tener esa saco pero claro Ahora
have to put it up,
hay que ponerlo
drill it and all that and the neighbor has to come
taladrar y todo eso y tiene que venir el
with the drill that he brought
vecino con el taladro que le ha traído
from the village, well, first
del pueblo bueno problemas del primer
world problems, no, you know, my terrace, I don't know
mundo no ya sabes mi terraza no sé por
why, I eat it made
qué la
of a certain material, I don't know if it's
como de un material no sé si será
infested, but
plagado eso pero
the wall is coming down, I don't know if I can hang
se viene la pared no sé si puedo colgar
anything, I have to, I have
cualquier cosa tengo que tengo tengo ahí
a few things pending to
unas cuantas de cosas pendiente que
hang on the terrace but I'm
colgar en el en la terraza pero yo soy
the worst part it's yours but the thing is that I
lo peor parte es tuya pero es que yo
live in a rented apartment, maybe I'll write to the landlord
vivo de alquiler igual escribo al casero
first Just in case, the
antes Por si acaso los agujeros
two holes, no, it doesn't have something strong to stop it from
dos no no lleva algo fuerte para que no
falling over, no, I mean, but the ceiling, let's see, I
se caiga no O sea pero va el techo A ver
want to put it on the terrace,
es que lo quiero poner la terraza modo
like I say, lunatic, and nobody can see me,
flipada como digo lunático y no me ve
well, it's like a brick wall,
nadie pues va es como ladrillo la pared
of course, since it's night, you can't see anything,
claro como estáis de noche no se ve nada
but then it seems to me that the screws
pero entonces me da como los tornillos
are like really big and it seems to me that you do
son como muy grandes y me da como cosa
n't know if the case will come and he's going to
no sabes si va a venir el caso y me va a
say, dear, the deposit will be paid
decir querida la fianza
first, but come on, I don't think you'll have any
antes pero vamos no creo que tengas
problems with hanging something that will be
problemas con con colgar una cosa que
solved later by covering up the grandparents
luego se soluciona tapando los abuelos
Pau Pau He tells me the other day I bought  things
Pau Pau Me dice el otro día compré cosas
and I don't know what happened with your store.
y no sé qué pasó en eso de tu tienda
Well, today I was talking
Pues precisamente hoy estuve hablando
to Juan López de Zárate who is the one who
con con Juan López de Zárate que es el
runs it and you know,
que la lleva y ya sabéis
yes,
sí
joking. It's all in the family. Here, let's see. I
broma Todo queda en familia aquí a ver
say the store. You go to my
lo digo la tienda entras en mi
chavalería.com. You go to the store and here you
chavalería.com vas a la tienda y aquí
have the store and you can buy. Okay,
tienes la tienda y puedes comprar vale
Juan runs it and you know that he is a
la lleva Juan que ya sabéis que es una
person I can completely trust. I mean, if not,
persona de plena confianza O sea si no
not a great person and a great person. And also,
no gran persona y gran persona y además
well, let's see for my birthday what are you
que bueno a ver para mi cumpleaños Qué
going to give me from all that. From there, look,
me vas a regalar de todo eso de ahí mira
what could be best for me? Being
lo que mejor me puede venir siendo
practical, it's because no, don't talk. I'm
práctica es porque no no hables
going to give you what comes out tomorrow.
te voy a regalar lo que sale mañana
That morning something comes out tomorrow something comes out that is
esa mañana sale algo mañana sale algo
perfect for you, like a couple from the
que te viene perfecto como pareja del
channel,
canal
an apron, something better, that. But if I don't
un delantal otra mejor eso pero si no
cook like a good woman, it's
cocino como buena mujer
canceled. Let's see, Juan doesn't have any
a canceladísimo a ver esto no lleva Juan
family. This. You're not going to have a problem
familia esto No vais a tener problema
with him. If I don't know if you have any
con él si yo que sé si tenéis algún
problem, you've paid and the product doesn't arrive,
problema que habéis pagado y no llega el
whatever it is, you write to Juan and let's go, you
producto lo que sea le escribís a Juan y
know, zero, let's go, zero
vamos ya sabéis que cero vamos cero
problems, you're going to have for sure today. He
problema vayas a tener segurísimo hoy Me
was talking to me. He more or less says that there are
estuvo hablando Más o menos dice que hay
some people who have already been buying.
algunas personas que han ido comprando
products and other stuff like that not much
ya productos y demás de esto no mucho
yet but something you can't imagine going
todavía pero algo no tú te imaginas ir
to Benidorm in the summer going to the portal and still seeing yourself
por benidorm en verano ir portal y verte
like that lady on the beach front
aún así señora en primera línea de playa
with a bag it's a beach of three sauces
con una bolsa es playa de tres salseos
that I'll lose my hair there yes I'll lose my
que me quedo sin pelo ahí sí que me
hair is that I put my hair in the
quedo sin pelo es que meto el pelo en la
bag
bolsa
this is your idea No yes that
esta es tu idea No sí que se vayan
people start meeting on the beach with him
encontrando la gente en la playa con el
with the subject no with the subject of
con el tema no con el tema de
[Music]
[Música]
that they recognize each other because they go with the
que se reconozcan porque van con los
bags at what time are we going to talk about what
bolsos a qué hora vamos a hablar de lo
Rocío Flores has told you because it has to do
que te ha dicho Rocío flores porque
with what you have been
tiene que ver con lo que tú has estado
considering and with what you have been
barajando y con lo que habéis estado
speculating in the sense that let's say that she has
especulando en el sentido de vamos que
given me an answer about her
me ha dado una respuesta a su futuro
professional future because we know that Marta is
profesional porque sabemos que Marta
coming to YouTube Antony David is on
llega a YouTube Antony David está en
YouTube and an Enigma was that we already
YouTube y un Enigma era que ya lo
talked about it in its day yes Rocío Flores is going to
hablamos en su día sí Rocío flores se va
make a YouTube channel
a hacer un canal de YouTube
and she has given me we
y ella me ha dado
have an answer it will be
tenemos respuesta
called I'm not afraid the channel will be
se va a llamar no tengo miedo el canal
called I'm not going to tell you anything What does
se va a llamar no os voy a decir nada
[Music] say
[Música]